The Pulse Chain ecosystem is absolutely
ripping right now. We have Hex on
PulseChain up 211% from the recent lows.
Hex on Ethereum up 100% from the lows.
Pulse is up 54% from the lows. Pulseex
is up 70% from the recent low. Inc is up
71% from the low. and and more on
PulseChain is up 594%
from the low. Let's talk about that one
first. We did some tweaks to the
website. You can now see the annualized
APY on all the chains. Right now on
Ethereum is 59% on PulseChain 61%. So a
lot of people are gaining confidence in
the Moore ecosystem seeing that the dev
me is actually building and sticking
with it. We had a huge runup on both
chains. So now we have the arbitrage
machine going. And if you don't know
what you're doing, I would say do not
mess around with the arbitrage, but
there is opp arbitrage opportunity if
you know what you're doing. Pretty easy
if you know what you're doing. Um so
that's taking effect. And so we have
we're having more up um 600% pretty much
now. There isn't much liquidity. Go
ahead and make put your liquidity jokes.
But we we have the solution for that
coming soon. and fuel. You see me talk
about fuel white papers at the top of
more tokens.com. And due to high demand,
I said I wasn't going to launch it on
Postchain. I actually didn't think it
would work on Postchain because of how
Postchain's base fees work, I think it
is. But after doing some more digging,
we're going to be launching Fuel on
Postchain. Yes. Yes. So, get your PLS
ready. Go check out the fuel white paper
at the top of more tokens.com and see
how it works. Wherever you see the word
ETH mentioned, just replace that with
pls and learn about it there. It's going
to be good. We're on test net right now
and it's it's addicting. Yeah. So, more
is up 600%. All right, let's go back.
Let's get back to some of the higher
caps on Pulse Chain. Let's start where
it all started with Hex. So, um, before
we get into this, I just want to say
there's a lot of negativity around
PulseChain because it's been it's been
beaten down so much. Let's read some of
that negativity. Cory Costa says,
"Flaunting being down 95% isn't the flex
you think it is since you want me to FUD
again." So, this postchain postnet
ecosystem
uh tagged this guy Cory Costa who's was
an avid postchain guy, but I guess he's
not really in the post chain anymore,
which understandably so. Um he reached
out to him kind of poking at him saying,
"Why aren't you flooding Postchain?" And
this is his response. Postchain is
trash. It's 34 number 34 in TVL. Most of
your call migrated to Richard Hart.
I don't know what he means by it. I
guess all of his coal the Cole in what
does Cole even stand for? Migrated to
Richard Hart. So I guess he means all
the influencers are now just Richard
Hart. So there aren't any influencers
anymore. The only person pumping the
chain is Richard to save what little
reputation he has left. The tablets
won't save you. Most of your old
streamers are gone. Provex has virtually
zero users. Most of the biggest daps
have extremely low TV or stop updating
their projects altogether. Your
infighting is insufferable to the
outside cryptosphere. Nobody wants
anything to do with this ecosystem. It
takes 45 minutes to bridge over to
Pulsechain using the official bridge.
You're up 25% from alltime low from the
last 5 years and you're celebrating.
There we go. I think I caught up on my I
think I caught up on my two months I
haven't discussed
what's left on this. What in the world
is he talking about? There we go. I
think I caught up on my two months I
haven't discussed what's left of this
hideous joke of an ecosystem. So, a lot
of valid points there. Um, a few that I
will I would punch back on is 34 and
TVL.
Here's the thing about this. Here's the
the approach you have to take with with
Postchain
and anything Richard Hart related or any
really this the approach I take with any
crypto really. TVL market cap marketing
maybe marketing a little bit but I enjoy
cryptos the most where I'm not really
concerned about marketing when I can
just do the thing like for hex you just
say stake you know and the yield that
you get from the hex stakes you know
you're getting yield the price of the
yield what the value of the yield is
going to be
you only really care about that based
off of your entry So, as long as your
entry is low enough, you don't really
have too much concern about what
somebody's going to do down the road.
Um, any marketing just becomes a bonus.
Most of the calls, oh, let's say most of
the influencers migrate to Richard Hart.
I see a good bit of postchain stuff.
Every now and then the algorithm starts
showing me postchain stuff. It was for a
little bit and then it kind of slowed
down again. Um same thing though like
all this this depending on influencers
you shouldn't be in anything where
you're def depending on influencers.
Um most of the biggest apps have
extremely low TV or stop updating their
projects altogether. More tokens.com
didn't do that. Um your infighting is
insufferable to the outside crypto. Now
I wouldn't say the infighting isn't
what's insufferable to me. What's
actually insufferable to me is the
constant positivity and the constant
brainwashing that goes on with Post
Shane. um people that are extremely loud
the entire time who were extremely loud
this entire time and now they want to be
loud at the bottoms and it's just cringe
where I hate to pat myself on the back
here but you have never ever heard me
say buy hex ever until the other day
that I wasn't saying buy hex but you
have never seen me heard me or seen me
say I'm buying hex I'm buying Hex here.
Hex is a good buy. Pulse is a good buy.
You never heard me say any of that. If
you did, it's probably a very rare
occurrence. Maybe it was like because it
was a crazy dip or something. But I was
always saying I was always the one
advocating nah, I wouldn't buy X. But
couple weeks, past couple months, I've
been buying Hex. I said it in the last
video before it started running. So,
let's look at the chart. So, this is Hex
on Ethereum. And we'll start with Hex on
Ethereum. Now,
sure, Hex is down a lot, you know, but I
mean, there is no real butt with that. I
would say, you know, hopefully you've
been selling, you know, hopefully you
weren't I mean, I got caught up in it,
too. I wish I would have emergency inst
everything at the top. the people that
did that and made out like bandits.
Like, man, I I I I regret it, but it's
not really, you know, something that I
would have never done because I didn't
do it. So, but now if you've been doing
that, you can buy the Hex back and man,
it does not take much to move the price
on any pair. 300,000 in liquidity on
Hex, you know, that's a lot of
liquidity. But for someone with millions
and millions, some of these guys, I
mean, if they played it right, they have
millions and millions to play with. I
mean, even me, I'm looking at it now,
it's like, I didn't buy a ton at the
lows and and in this range.
Um, but if it pulls back, I might make a
big stake, you know, like um, and it's
not even because of the price in
increase potential. Like, I'm not even
I'm not even trying to advocate for
that. I'm advocating for how down it is
being that it's so down. I'm sure it
could go down more, but kind of like
what I talked about with Wise, it's
become so it's been so long and it's
down so much that you can stake and
you're and if you stake for a long
enough time, if you're building a ladder
out, kind of like what I'm even doing on
more tokens.com, just building a ladder
out with these massive long stakes and
just doing that consistently over time
your yield will probably outperform any
downside that it took. So even if I
stake for SAS stake for 10 years and it
goes all the way down here this keeps
going down down down down by the time I
get that stake the hex that I earned
it's going to give me some ROI in USD
terms potentially it's not guaranteed
but that's kind of my approach with hex.
like it's a way for me to put funds out
in the future for emergency for rainy
days for for dip buying. The problem
with hex is you kind of got to pick one.
You got to pick you don't really have
to, but is it going to be hex on
ethereum or hex on postchain? I lean
towards hex on on ETH because I know ETH
is going to be around for the the length
of my stake. I know fees are probably
going to keep getting cheaper on ETH, so
I'm not really concerned about fees
anymore, but then you have Hex on
Pulsechain where that's pretty much
where all the the activity is. And
[clears throat] I think we we can see
that Hex on Pulse is already
outperforming the Ethereum version. and
it could be the one that ultimately
takes off, but at the same time,
I don't think they're going to go
um they're going to leave each other
because if you think about it, it's the
same thing with more. It's got that
arbitrage opportunity. So, people can
bridge and keep I'm sure there's a pool
for it where hex and postchain hex are
paired together. So that's why they kind
of move together.
Um but of course one is going to
outperform the other. So same thing
that's happening with Moore. Mo more is
up 500% on PC chain and on Ethereum it's
up 300 and we'll say 400%. So you got to
pick your poison. Um I don't think it
really matters. I just think it just
depends on how comfortable you want to
be.
Um, Pulse Chain is still it. We're
having a run now, but I mean, remember
how it was like a couple weeks ago, like
the bridges and all the FUD and you
never know what's going to happen. You
got to weigh all that stuff out. I
honestly think there are better buys in
general. You should just buy Bitcoin.
Imagine you were just buying Bitcoin.
Um, you can just do that. Um, I think
Hex and Pulse Chain and stuff should be
a small
side of what you do. That's how I
operate. It's a small portion of what I
do. I love seeing it going up. Um, so
let's chart a little bit. Where does
Pulse Chain need to go? So, let's This
This is Hex. So, let's see. We've got a
nice reversal. I would say Postchain
actually has the nicest reversal
potential. It's already kind of cleared
some recent levels, but I would say this
level right here is that's the level
that I would say, okay, we're turning
around and we're looking like we're
turning around, but it's not confirmed
yet. We could still stop here and fall.
And we never really
made any reversal, but we got some lows,
we got higher lows. It's looking good. I
will say that. But it's only looking
good if you've been buying. If you
haven't really bought anything, then
you're kind of FOMOing right now, right?
Um, so I would not be Here we go. I
would not be I am not buying
OC Chain or Hex or anything today. If
I'm going to get some, it's going to be
on the next pullback. And the next
pullback, I'm going to be super patient.
Now, usually what happens is if it's
bullish, you don't really get pullbacks.
It just keeps running. It keeps looking
like it's going to dip and then it
doesn't. It makes little candles like
this where it's oscillating around,
oscillating around, and just takes off
again. So,
probably not going to get any dips. Um,
if it's bullish, if it's not bullish, I
would be looking for the first warning,
it's not bullish, would be a candle that
just wipes away a previous day's
candles. So something like this right
here. You see that if you go around,
look on the charts, any chart, and if
you see a a green candle and then
another candle that's way bigger than it
going down, it's usually almost always
followed by down. Now, it didn't happen
here, but it happened here.
Call almost call that one.
There's one. There's one. There's one.
So, you know, you can when when I when I
get that signal right there, that's when
I'll say, "Okay, it's time to get ready
to, you know, well, I mean, take profit
if you're if you've traded and you've
made some gains." But, um, this could be
another opportunity to get out. Would I
be selling here? I would just, if you
held on this long, I don't I don't know
why you're selling. Um, you might as
well just hold on. Yeah, this is
definitely a buyer market for Pulse
Chain. It's really beating down from
where it was. And if you just think
about the supply, you think about who
has all the coins. Fully diluted market
cap for P 65 million. So the real fully
diluted market cap is probably like 6
million. It's a lot lower than you know
what it looks like. If you think about
who has coins, Richard Hart probably has
90 I think. I can't remember, but it's
probably like 90%. So that means you
could just go ahead and factor his coins
out of it because he's not going to be
dumping. I mean, I don't think so. The
real market cap would be around 6
million, which is actually pretty
incredible.
So it just made a move up when I said
that. So
yeah, it's a really small chain that's
kind of bursting at the scenes because
there is a lot of there are a lot of
users. Post chains has a lot of people
and if it starts going up, it's not
going to stop because people are going
to get louder and louder and louder and
louder and um yeah, so for me, I haven't
been buying pulse. I just been keeping
my post in VLS.
Um that's my way to buy post on the way
down. Um I kind of want to buy some
though, but I'm just trying to resist my
FOMO right now. It's not a good time to
buy. Um, but if we do pull back, where
would I be buying? Pulse chain or hex on
the next pullback. If we pull back to
these levels back here, I won't FOMO and
start buying, but I really want to see
what happens with these two lows here.
Um, what I would like to see is, of
course, I would like to just see it pump
and break through here and create a new
support level here and build. Um, but
the buyer in me would like to see it
stall out and come back down to these
levels and hold these two lows. Maybe,
you know, get close. Maybe five zeros
and the six, five, 59. get close to it
and then start to work its way back up.
Um,
but I ultimately want to see these
levels. This level here hold. That's
about it. Check out more tokens.com.
Make use some stakes. Do a ladder. Ay is
actually higher than post higher than
Hex. So, there's that. And it's got a
cap supply and there's a buy and burn
coming. So, I would say check it out.
Um, not financial advice.
Um, but it is my crypto. It's my
favorite crypto. And yeah, what are you
guys doing? Do you guys think this is a
fake pump? Let me know in the comments.
And I'll talk to you in the next one.
Peace.